No?
ダ メ?
Well then, you're opening your own pussy.
じゃあさ、自分でさ、自分でおまんこ開いてるじゃん
Here, yes.
こ っち、そう
Isn't it?
ないでしょ?
By yourself.
自分で
Oh, that's amazing.
あ、すっげーろい
Wow, wow.
うわ、やば
Hey, have you ever done a pose like this?
え、こんなポーズしたことある?
There isn't.
ないよね
It's so beautiful
すっげーきれいで
Sho.
しょ
Oh, wow.
あ、 やば
No, right?
ないでしょ
Hey, have you ever done a pose like this?
え、こんなポーズしたことある?
Eh, amazing.
えー、すごい
That's amazing.
すごいね
yeah?
ん?
Let me show you now.
もうお見せましょう
It's over.
もう終わり
No, no, wait a minute.
いやいやいや、ちょっと待ってよ
Because I haven't seen it yet.
まだ見てないから
I've already seen it myself.
もう、自分で見ました
I haven't seen it, I haven't seen it.
見てない、見てない
I saw it, I saw it.
見ました、見ました
Let's end this now.
もう終わりにしましょう
I'm going home too.
私も帰ります
That's all.
もうここまでです
That's a bit cold.
それはちょっと冷たいじゃん
You already took the picture, right?
もう撮ったじゃないですか
A little more, not yet.
もうちょい、まだ
You didn't say the time.
時間言ってないでしょ
How much should I take?
どんだけ撮るかって
I'm done now so I'm going home.
もう 終 わったんで帰ります
I'm going home.
帰ります
Don't go home.
帰ないで
No.
ダメです
I'm going home now, so I'll just get the money and go home.
もう帰るんでお金だけもらって帰ります
No, I can't give it to you yet, so it's money.
いやいや、まだ渡せないからお金に
I think so.
それ思います
No, I haven't taken any pictures yet.
いやいや、まだ撮ってないんだもんだって
You took the picture, right?
撮ったじゃないですか
No, it's still a finish that goes to the pussy, isn't it?
いや、まだマンツコ行く仕上がりじゃないですか
I'm about to get dressed.
もうもうもう、服着ます
I'll get dressed and go home.
服着て帰ります
No, no, don't go home.
いやいや、帰んないでね
Don't go home, really.
帰んないでね、ほんと
Seriously.
まじで
Not yet.
まだまだ
Hey, I took a photo.
ちょっとね、撮っちゃったから
This data has not been deleted yet.
まだこれ消してないデータ
You want to erase it, right?
消したいでしょ
that's right.
そうです
You promised to erase it.
消すって約束したでしょ
It won't go away, if it stays like this.
消えないよ、このままじゃ
Is it okay?
いいの?
I don't have this.
これ持ってないって
This way.
このまんま
I already took all the pictures, but it's me.
もう全部撮ったけど、俺
Well, that's a different story, isn't it?
話違うじゃないですか、だって
No, I'm the one saying something different.
いやいや、話違うこと言ってるの自分じゃん
No, because even at the beginning, the lower banks are no good either.
いや、だってもう、最初だって、下銀もダメって話とか
But, you know, it's a matter of giving each other money and agreeing to it.
でもそれは、ほら、お互いね、お金を渡して納得するっていう話で
You said you were going to do it, right?
や るってなったでしょ?
it is.
それは
That's what I'm saying is good.
自分がいいって言ってる、それ
So I guess I'm done shooting now.
だからもう撮って終わりじゃないですか
Yeah, that's why I haven't shot it yet.
うん、だからまだ撮ってないって話
Didn't you just take the picture?
今撮ったじゃないですか
I was told it was no good because I dropped it from there.
そこから落としたからダメって話で、
Let's put an end to money.
お金も終わりにしましょう
No, I'm still talking about time.
いや、時間とかまだ言ってる
I haven't been able to take any pictures, so I have to take a lot of pictures.
撮れてないから、いっぱい撮んなきゃいけないから、
Please feel free to adjust it to your fundas.
それは勝手にファンダースに合わせてください
it is.
それは
That was decided by the two of you, right?
それは2人で決めたことでしょ?
No, I haven't decided yet.
いや、決めてないです
No, I've decided.
いや、決めたじゃん
You said it yourself.
自分で言ったじゃん、それ
Eh, I didn't say anything.
え、言ってないです、何も
I told you that.
言ったじゃん、それは
Tell me you can take a picture.
撮っていいです、言って
I'll give you the money, so you want the money, right?
お金渡すから、お金欲しいでしょ?
I want money, but it's no good.
お金欲しいですけど、でもダメです
I went home.
私帰りました
Don't go home, that's it.
帰らないで、それは
still.
まだ
I haven't taken any pictures yet.
まだ撮ってないんだけど
No.
ダメです
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Because this is it.
もう、だってこれ
It's fine as it is, so why don't you take this data home with you?
このままだから、いいんで、これデータ持って帰る?
this.
これ
Because it's different from the promise.
約束と違うからさ
Bring this data home.
これ、データ持って帰ってさ
That's no good.
それはダメです
My friends are watching.
友達が見てる
No.
ダメです
Please delete that.
それは消してください
Game Eight knows.
ゲームエイトが知ってるわ
No, no.
いや、いやです
Is that why you want to delete it?
だから消したいんでしょ?
So that's it, um, just follow.
だからそれはもう、あの、ちょっと従ってください
Right?
でしょ?
Yeah, will it be over soon?
うん、すぐ終わりますか
horse.
うま
Are you satisfied?
満足した?
I'll run this.
流しますよ、これ
No.
ダメです
It is no good to flush it.
流すのはダメです
Wait a minute, then.
ちょっと、じゃあ
Open something, again.
なんか開いて、また
Open it.
開いて
horse.
うま
Delicious, delicious.
おいしい、おいしい
Oh no.
やば
Delicious, delicious.
おいしい、おいしい
good,
いい、
Good, good.
いい、 いい
Don't touch me.
触らないで
I haven't touched it.
触ってない
You can't touch it.
触 って ない じゃない の
I'm already touching it.
もう、触っている
What are you saying now?
何言うてんの、今?
You didn't touch it, right?
触ってないでしょ?
No.
ダメです
I haven't touched it, so it's fine.
触ってないから、いいよ
I haven't touched it.
触ってないです
delicious.
美味しい
No.
ダメ
It was really delicious, and I was really impressed with it.
めちゃめちゃ美味しい、なんかめっちゃズームが取ってた
No way.
やだ
rainwear.
うい
You didn't touch it, did you?
触ってないでしょ
Don't touch it now.
触 って ない で しょ、 今
You're not touching it now, are you?
触ってないでしょ、今
Don't touch it now.
触 って ない で しょ、今
I'm licking it now.
舐めてんだよ、今
delicious.
美味しい
I don't like it.
嫌です
I don't like it, I don't like it
嫌だ、嫌
is.
だ
Biting honey
噛 みつ
there was.
いた
I don't like it.
嫌 だ
I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ、嫌だ
I'm licking it now.
舐 めて んだよ、今
Yeah.
うん
Delicious, delicious.
美味しい、美味しい
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I'll run this.
流すよ、これ
No.
ダメ
No?
ダメ?
Well then, just a little more.
じゃあ、もうちょっと
Hear good things.
いい こと 聞 いて
Hear something good.
いいこと聞いて
Look.
ほら
It's wet.
濡れてるじゃん
It's like this, right?
こんな感じでしょ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
That's a lie.
嘘だ
He's probably sleeping.
寝てるもんだって
I don't get angry.
怒 らない
He's sleeping.
寝てるじゃん
It's like this, right?
こんな感じでしょ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
I'm sleeping.
寝てる
Look.
ほら
I can hear your voice.
声にヌヌしてる
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ
Open it.
開けて
No more.
もう、ダメ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I'll run this.
流すよ、これ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
No.
ダメ
I can't do it anymore.
もう、無理
I really don't like it.
本当に嫌だ
Why?
なんでだよ
Impossible.
無理
Impossible, impossible.
無 理、無理
I can't do it anymore.
無理、もう
No, you're saying you don't like it.
ダメ、嫌だって言ってるじゃん
Wait a minute, that's not true.
ちょっと 待って、それは違うでしょ
Not close, not close.
近 くない、近くない
That's different, isn't it?
それは違うでしょ
a little bit.
ちょっと
I told you so.
言 ったじゃん
I'm going home.
帰る
Go home, call the police.
帰る、警察呼ぶ
Wait a minute.
ちょっと待ってよ
If you do that, it'll be different.
それやったら、違うでしょ
I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ、嫌だ、嫌だ
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
Well then, let's finish quickly.
じゃあ、早く終わろう
I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ、嫌だ
Also, just a little bit.
あと、ちょっとね
If you listen to me, I'll be kind to you.
言 うこと聞いてくれたら、優しくするし
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Because it's over,
終 わるから、
It's better to end it lightly, right?
薄 く終わるほうがいいでしょ
I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ、嫌だ
Because it's over, no, no.
終わるから、 違う、違う
It's better to end up thin, right?
薄く終わるほうがいいでしょ
Dislike
嫌
No, I don't like it.
だ、 嫌だ
What is this?
何これ?
Hey, hey, hey.
ちょっと、ほら、ほら
That's a lie.
嘘だ
It looks a little painful.
ちょっと、痛そう
What is this?
何これ?
yeah?
ん?
Hey, hey, hey.
ちょっと、ほら、ほら
Open, open.
開け、開け
I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ、嫌だ、嫌だ
I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌 だ、嫌だ
嫌だ、嫌だ
It won't end.
終わんない
Because it won't end.
終 わんないから
Seriously.
マ ジで
Wow, it's coming out.
すごい、出てきてる
It's coming out.
出てきてる
Soup.
お汁が
yeah?
ん?
What is this?
何これ?
Soup.
お汁がさ
delicious.
おいしい
It's delicious.
おいしいわ
amazing.
すごい
It disappeared.
消えたって
Only myself.
自分だけ
Just touch, touch.
ちょっと、触って、触って
It'll be over soon.
終わるから、すぐ
I'll let it flow, after all.
流すよ、だって
You don't like it, do you?
嫌でしょ
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
Well then.
じゃあ
It's better for it to end, right?
終わるほうがいいでしょ
I don't like either of them.
どっちも嫌だ
Oh yeah, yeah.
そうそう、そうそう
Send it.
送って
I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ、嫌だ、嫌だ
what?
何?
You already know.
もう分かるでしょ
What should I do?
どうしたらしてくるの?
I don't like it.
嫌
oh yeah.
そうそう
Please be kind.
優しくやってくれ
I'll finish it right away.
すぐ終わってあげるから
Please do it properly.
ちゃんとやってくれ
It's okay if you're not good at it.
下手でもいいから
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Squeeze your hands.
手をしごいて
Properly.
ちゃん と
That's it.
そんな
Where did you learn it?
どこで覚えたの?
Squeeze it properly.
しごいて、ちゃんと
With my knees, with my knees, properly.
膝で、膝で、ちゃんと
He's a good boy.
いい子だね
Let go.
手を離す
Lick it while looking at me.
こっち見ながら舐めて
Yes, you're good at it.
そう、上手じゃん
Oh, that's amazing.
ああ、すごい
He's a good boy.
いい子だね
I'm not going to rest for a while.
ちょっと休んないね
Ah, I'm excited.
あ、興奮する
Exciting, amazing.
興奮する、すげえ
I'm excited.
興奮するわ
Oh no, already.
やべえ、もう
Oh no, no
やべえ、やべ
picture.
え
It feels good.
気 持ちいいね
Squeeze, squeeze.
しごいて、しごいて
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
You're good at it.
上手いね
Good, good, good.
上 手 い、 上手い、上手い
Stretch it out.
伸ばして
Look.
ほら
What happened?
なんとなっちゃった
Do it properly.
ちゃんとして
I licked it.
舐めんだよ
deep.
深い
Deep, deep.
深い、深い
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Can I wash it?
洗っていい?
It felt so good.
めっちゃ気持ちよかった
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Do your eyes hurt?
目痛い?
I turned red.
赤くなったよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's just a little too disgusting.
もうちょっと気持ち悪すぎてさ
Are you excited?
興奮しちゃったのか
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Do you think so?
思ってる?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
it is.
それは
I'll give you the money properly.
ちゃんとお金渡すし
I love you.
愛するんで
I showed you a little bit.
ちょっとだけ見せた
Really already.
もう本当に
Really.
本当に
a bit.
少 し
nice.
いいね
That's it.
ここまでね
Once you have taken the picture.
撮っちゃったらもう
Let's do it together.
一緒にしよう
You're good at blowjobs.
フェラ上手いね
No one sat down.
誰にも座ったんだ
That's it.
そんな
picture?
え?
Not sitting.
座ってない
I definitely sat down.
座ったじゃん、絶対
producer?
プロデューサー?
I want to drink just a little more.
もうちょっとだけ飲みたい
You love blowjobs, for sure.
フェラ好きっしょ、絶対
You're talking about your own body.
自分の体って言ってんじゃん
I absolutely love it.
絶対好きだよね
It still feels good.
まだ気持ちいい
I absolutely love you, Fela.
絶対好きだよ、フェラ
Erotic, right?
エロいでしょ
Let me sleep for a while.
ちょっと寝させて
No.
ダメ
Well, now that we've come this far.
いやいや、もうここまで来たら
No, no.
違います、ダメ
No, no, we're already together.
いやいや、もう一緒じゃん
No.
ダメ
That's fine.
いいじゃん
a little bit.
ちょっと
No.
ダメ
We're together.
一緒じゃん
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
No, no.
ダメ、ダメ
Why not?
なんでダメなの?
It's not decided why it's not good, right?
なんでってダメって決まってないでしょ、
Especially.
別に
No.
ダメです
We're already together, that's it.
もう一緒じゃん、そこは
I can still go.
まだ行けるんだもん
Oh no.
やば
Please, please.
お願い、お願い
So, give me money.
だから、お金をね
Well, double that.
じゃあ、倍
I'll pay double.
倍払いますよ
times.
倍
This is twice as much.
これ倍ですよ
Double this.
これの倍
Have a look?
見てみ?
Look inside?
中を見てみ?
It's double this.
これの倍だよ
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけで
Five or six minutes left.
あと5、6分
Maybe two or three minutes.
2、3分かもしれない
Please put on the rubber.
ゴムつけてください
Can I wear rubber?
ゴムつけてはいい?
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
rubber.
ゴム
sorry.
ごめんなさい
I put on rubber for the first time in a while.
ゴム、久しぶりにつける
If you put rubber on it, you won't know.
ゴムをつけたら分かんないんだよ
Put it on.
つけて
I don't understand.
私は分かんないです
You get it.
分かるでしょ
picture?
え?
You get it.
分かるでしょ
It's this way.
こっちだよ
I'll react.
反応してあげる
Should I wear rubber?
ゴムつけたらいいの?
I don't like it.
嫌だし
I don't know.
分かんないよ
It's been a while.
久しぶりに
I'm always raw though.
俺いつも生なんだけどさ
It's been a long time since I put it on.
めちゃめちゃ久しぶりにつけた
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
It's fresh.
新鮮だわ
Kocchi
こ っち
Yes.
だ よ
Feels good.
気持ちいい
That's amazing.
すごいね
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
Idolman child.
アイドルマン子
Feels good.
気 持 ち いい
feeling
気 持 ち
good.
いい
Let's do it with pets.
ペ ットでさ、やろう
good?
いい?
A real man?
目大丈夫?
Push me out.
押しつけ出してくれ
This way
こ っち向
Stay.
いて
Come up here.
こ っち上来て
That's amazing.
すごいじゃん
You can do it properly.
ちゃんとできるじゃん
Won't you move?
動いてくれない?
Properly.
ちゃんと
Will you please move?
動 いてくれない?
Properly.
ちゃんと
amazing.
すごい
good luck.
頑張ってね
Move.
動いて
Okay.
オッケー
Please move.
動いてくれ
feeling
気持
Good.
ち いい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
My voice is coming out.
声出てるよ
why?
なんで?
My voice is coming out.
声出てるよ
picture?
え?
Should I just leave?
出てばいいでしょ?
feelings
気 持
Good.
ち いい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Can I take it out?
出していい?
Can I cum inside you?
中出していい?
Can I take it out?
出していい?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I'm sorry.
ご めんね
I haven't put it out.
出してないよ
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
I cried.
泣いちゃった
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Sorry.
ごめんね
Because I haven't released it.
出してないからね
Should I wash it there?
そっちで洗おうか
eye.
目
You did your best.
頑張ったね
Because it's okay now.
もう大丈夫だから
Because I don't.
しないから
Let's shake hands.
握手しよ
It's cold.
冷たって
Cold.
冷た